energetic
and
hurried
in
a
british
accent
Jesus
talked
about
HELL
more
than
anyone
else!
What
He
said
will
SHOCK
you!
Everyone
thought
they
knew
who
was
going
to
hell...
But
Jesus
said
the
RELIGIOUS
people
would
fill
it!
The
ones
praying
on
street
corners
for
show...
Jesus
said
THEY'D
be
first
in
line!
While
the
prostitutes
and
tax
collectors
got
saved!
He
wept
because
religion
WITHOUT
relationship
leads
to
hell!
Are
you
just
playing
church
or
do
you
KNOW
Him?
Jesus
said
many
will
say
"Lord,
Lord"
but
He'll
say
"I
never
knew
you!"
It's
not
about
being
religious
-
it's
about
being
REAL!
Type
AMEN
if
you
want
REAL
relationship
with
Jesus!
Subscribe
for
more
truth!