You're not graduating this year. And deep down, you knew that. Let's not pretend this was some twist ending. This was always the plot. What were you even doing? Sleeping through deadlines like they were soft jazz? Watching productivity videos like osmosis was a strategy. You failed your final exam? LOL. The questions weren't even hard. Just long.
like your list of excuses, and shorter than your attention span. Your thesis? Let's talk about it. What even was your argument? That you kind of read some of the material, sort of got the gist, and hoped ChatGPT would carry you? Let's be honest. If ChatGPT did your defense, you'd have graduated with honors. Instead, we got you.
mumbling through your slides like you were allergic to coherence. And don't get mad when I say this, but halfway through your presentation, even your PowerPoint gave up and crashed. It knew. We all did. Your friends are graduating. Your name's not even on the list. Not because they forgot, but because you never made it past the footnotes of your own story. But hey,
Failure builds character, right? You'll be so interesting to future employers as a cautionary tale. You told yourself you'd bounce back. Start fresh next semester. New year, new you. But it's May. You're still revising. Whatever that means now. Productivity hacks won't save you. Neither will coffee.
Pomodoro timers, or that one YouTuber who yells at you to grind while you cry into your ramen. Here's the part no one says out loud. Maybe this just isn't for you. Not school, not success, not trying at things. You gave it a shot. The shot missed. Hit the ceiling fan. It's okay though. Take another year off.
call it a sabbatical, or self-discovery, or depression, but make it aesthetic on your stories. You want a shortcut? A cheat code? Here it is. Stop pretending effort works when you never applied it. Miracles don't scale. Neither do pity extensions. They're not mad. They're not disappointed. They're just done.
Your professors won't even remember your name. You were a blurry box on a laggy screen for three semesters straight. Maybe you should talk to someone. Or maybe you already did, and lied through your teeth about how you're working on it. Sure you are. Me too. This isn't a setback. It's a pattern. You're not unlucky. You're consistent.
consistently just below minimum standards. Graduation's a ceremony, not a miracle. It doesn't come with a participation medal or a do-over. It just moves on, with or without you. This was the part where you were supposed to prove them wrong, but you didn't even show up for the scene. You let the montage fade out before the climax. So, now what?
You re-enroll, try again, or maybe you just keep lying to your parents for one more semester, one more deadline you'll miss. But hey, don't feel bad. You still learn something. How to pretend, how to hope, how to coast. It's just nobody gives you a degree for that. So, here's your diploma, a reality check.
You didn't pass the test, but you're still here, and that means you get to try again. Or don't. Honestly, nobody's watching.