Boy, look at you. Just look at you. Ain't got no job, no money, no bitches, no drive, just vibes and body odor. You sittin' in the same crusty-ass boxers smellin' like broken promises and hot Cheeto dust. Bum-ass nigga. You out here double-tappin' baddies with a minor $17 bank account. No hoes, no dough, no goals. Nigga, you a financial ghost. A broke-ass spirit. You scaring your own money away.
You out here googling jobs that pay hella but don't require effort. Bro, you ain't lookin' for employment, you lookin' for a miracle. Get your lazy shortcuts searchin' can't read the fine print ass off my wifi. You so broke you out here makin' struggle smoothies, tap waterin' vibes talkin' about Balkan season. Balkan for what? You ain't even liftin' responsibility, dog-ass nigga.
Your resume looked like it was typed by a drunk possum, spelled professional as professional. Nigga, even all the correct gave up on you. You got chat GPT and still sound like a dropout. Dusty keyboard using ass. All your homies bossing up and here you go. The designated, yo, that's lit, friend.
You everybody's cheerleader cause you ain't got no motion. You clapping at other folks' success like that's your LinkedIn endorsement. No path having ass. Boy, you sitting there trying to manifest money with incense and vibes? Nigga, you need to manifest a schedule. Ain't no vision boy saving you from poverty. That's not the law of attraction. That's the law of ain't shit.
You trying to finesse the system but can't even finesse a basic sentence. You lied on your resume and still ain't get hired. Even the lies weren't convincing. You a fraud and a failure, nigga. Every morning you give yourself that little pep talk. We gon' get it. Bro, it's June. You been gon' get it since January. Lying to yourself with confidence. Narcissists with no achievements.
You out here telling shorties you between jobs like that sounds sexy. Boy, you been between jobs for two damn years. What you between? Hope and depression? No hoes getting ass, nigga. A recruiter slid in your inbox and you left them on red like you to catch.
Boy, you unemployed. You ain't playin' hard to get, you just hard to employ. You allergic to opportunity, dumbass nigga. Your calendar say grind hard, shine later, but all you done this money is smoke and play 2K. You ain't grindin', you glitchin'. You livin' like a side-quest character in GTA. You out here musty, unemployed, and still somehow cocky. No deodorant, no income, maximum ego. Nigga, you stink and broke. That's a federal crime.
You got asked what motivates you, and you said hunger. Boy, if you don't shut your poetic, starving artist, rhyming-powered ass up, motivation ain't enough. Get skills, dummy. You wrote self-taught visionary on your resume like that means something. You're not a visionary. You're just unemployed with Wi-Fi and ideas that don't pay rent, hallucinating success having ass.
You watchin' people quit jobs you ain't even qualified to apply for. Nigga, you ain't stuck in the Matrix. You never logged in. You a background character in your own life. Shorty asked what you doin', you said, I'm workin' on me. Nah, you workin' on nothin'. You unemployed with a self-care routine and no self-respect. Get off them crystals and fill out a W-2, nigga.
You left sticky notes with motivational quotes like that's gonna change your situation. You motivational but broke. You inspirational but useless. You broke Gandhi ass nigga. The version of you who got it together, he disgusted. He looking at you like, damn bro, you still here? Still broke? Still blaming capitalism when you can't even spell resume?
I ain't even mad no more. I'm just disappointed. You could've been somethin', but you rather scroll, smoke, and pretend. So keep playin'. No job havin', no hoes gettin', no goal-settin' bum-ass nigga. The world movin', and you, you still on pause.