I think it was a dream, but it didn't feel like one. The bed wasn't on the floor. It was above water. The ceiling watched me sleep. There was a calendar. Every day was today. The handwriting said it was mine, but I've never written like that. It curled wrong. I tried to leave. There was no door. Just a frame.
When I stepped through, I came back in from above. I was already in the bed, sleeping. The coffee whispered something in a voice I knew from childhood nightmares. The steam spelled words I forgot as soon as I looked away. I opened the closet. The coats were upside down, hanging from sleeves, and they were breathing. I think they knew I was watching.
There was a photo on the wall, a family, my family, I think, but my face was just static. Everyone else was pointing, smiling too wide. I looked outside. The ground was sky. The sky was dirt. Trees grew down from it, like roots. One of them waved at me. The TV was stuck on one image.
Me, screaming, over and over. My mouth moved, but there was no sound. Just the ticking of the house. The mirror didn't show me now. It showed me as a child, crying, mouthing something. I pressed my hand to the glass, and he screamed. I climbed the stairs. They folded up like paper behind me.
There were feet at the top, bare feet, but nobody's just waiting. The fridge was full of clocks. No food, just time, arguing with itself. One ticked backwards. I think it was mine.
There was a book on the table, pages filled with photos, all of me sleeping from angles that don't exist. I ran down the hall, but I had two shadows, one that moved late, one that smiled without a face when I didn't look directly at it. In my room, someone had drawn a door in crayon. It was slightly open, light spilled out.
It hummed like my name, but not how it should sound. There was a cake. My birthday, I think. Too many candles melting backward into tiny wax people. They all looked like me. Someone was under the blanket. I pulled it back. Nothing, but the sheet stayed heavy. It breathed when I touched it.
I found a note, wake up, but the letters were fading every time I blinked until only up was left, and then, not even that. I woke up, I think, but I was still in the bed, on the screen. I watched myself wake up, over and over, each time, more wrong, less human.
I saw myself in a puddle, not here, somewhere else, sleeping, wired up, mouth sown shut, but my eyes, they were wide open.
And then I found the room, full of beds, full of me, every bed, another me, all whispering at once, don't wake her. And I understood, I'm not dreaming, I'm the dream, she's still asleep, I'm just the noise her brain makes when she turns too deep.
If you're fearing this, then she's waking up. And you're part of it now. Look in the mirror. Tell me whose face you see.