I didn't remember renting the house. I just woke up in it. The walls were warm. They shouldn't have been warm. There were photos on the mantle. A family. A woman holding a baby. But when I blinked, her face was gone. Just skin. Just smooth, stretched skin. And I thought, maybe that's normal.
I looked into the mirror and saw the back of my head until it turned slowly, too slowly, and smiled at me. It had my teeth, but too many. At dinner, I heard whispering under the table, not voices,
breathing. I didn't move. I just whispered back. Not tonight. And it stopped. The fridge didn't have food. It had photographs, wet, stuck together, each one of a face, blurry, melting, like they were trying to forget themselves. There was something in the bedroom corner.
a mannequin, but sometimes I'd wake up and its arms had moved just a little, just enough to notice, like it wanted me to catch it changing. The phone rang every night at 3.33 am when I answered. It didn't speak, it breathed, and once
I swear it licked my ear. I unplugged the TV, but it stayed on. Static faces flickering. Faces I'd seen before. In dreams. In mirrors. Behind my eyelids when I blinked too long. There were drawings on the wall.
Crayons, child's handwriting, they drew me, being dragged underground, smiling stick people holding my arms, the word HOME, written in red. The ceiling taps back.
Sometimes, I tap once, and it taps three times. Morse code, I translated it once. It's spelled soon. The clocks don't tell time anymore. The hands spin, but the numbers, god, the numbers keep shifting into letters. They always say, her. One night, I saw myself at the end of the hall, but I didn't move.
The other me did, and I smiled, and it smiled back, and I swear, it whispered, you're almost ready. Then I remembered her, the woman.
The one from the photo. She came to dinner one night, sat down across from me. She had no face, but I recognized her. I asked, are you my wife? And she nodded. She said, you were supposed to stay asleep. She didn't say it with a mouth. She said it inside my bones. And I remembered. I remembered. I'm not awake.
I never was. I'm inside her. Inside the house. Inside the loop. I'm a memory she keeps reliving. Every night. Every nightmare. I'm not the real one. I was never me. I was her. I am her. And she wants out. And if you're hearing this, she found a new face.