There's
no
grand
lesson
here.
No
moment
of
clarity.
Just
another
night
that
bleeds
into
another
morning
that
doesn't
matter.
Everyone's
moving,
talking,
smiling,
but
it's
all
noise.
No
one's
really
here.
They
never
were.
Nothing
sticks.
I
keep
trying
to
remember
faces,
but
even
the
memories
rot.
Everyone
I
ever
loved
feels
like
a
dream
I
lied
about
having.
They
say,
you'll
be
okay.
But
they're
just
trying
to
calm
themselves.
Nobody
really
knows
what
they're
doing.
They're
just
scared
you'll
say
what
they're
thinking.
Hope
feels
fake
now,
like
a
commercial.
Bright
colors
over
a
dead
signal.
I
can't
even
pretend
to
believe
in
it
anymore.
And
honestly,
I
don't
miss
it.
Some
nights,
I
wonder
what
it
would
feel
like
to
disappear,
not
in
some
dramatic
way,
just
quietly,
like
smoke,
static
fading
out.
And
if
someone
found
this,
this
voice,
thought,
I
don't
think
it
would
matter.
They'd
just
scroll
past,
skip,
forget,
we
all
do.
We
keep
looking
forward
like
there's
something
coming,
like
there's
a
break
in
the
sky,
but
there's
not.
There
never
was.
Sometimes
the
exit
is
just
another
room.
Same
shape,
same
silence,
new
wallpaper,
nothing
changes.
You
won't
be
remembered,
neither
will
I.
We
were
here,
and
then
we
weren't,
and
the
world
won't
even
flinch.
If
you're
listening,
don't
look
for
hope
here.
There's
none.
Just
the
truth.
Just
the
quiet.
Just
the
end.