Gather
'round,
child.
Got
a
story
Jesus
told
in
Matthew
thirteen.
About
seeds
and
soil.
Been
farmin'
most
my
life
—
this
one
hits
deep.
Jesus
sat
by
the
water,
crowds
pressin'
in.
Told
'em
about
a
sower
who
went
out
to
plant.
Now
this
farmer,
he
scattered
seed
everywhere.
Didn't
pick
and
choose
where
it
fell.
Some
fell
on
the
path
—
hard
ground,
beaten
down.
Birds
came
quick
and
snatched
it
up.
Other
seeds
hit
rocky
places.
Sprouted
fast
in
shallow
dirt,
looked
promising
at
first.
But
when
the
sun
got
hot,
they
withered.
No
deep
roots
to
draw
from.
Some
fell
among
thorns.
Started
growin'
good,
then
got
choked
out
by
weeds.
But
the
seed
that
hit
good
soil?
Lord
have
mercy
—
thirty,
sixty,
a
hundred
times
what
was
planted.
Later,
disciples
asked,
"What's
it
mean,
Master?"
They
were
scratched
their
heads
like
we
do.
Jesus
said,
"The
seed
is
God's
Word.
But
the
soil
—
that's
the
human
heart."
The
hard
path?
That's
a
closed
heart.
Word
bounces
right
off.
Satan
comes
quick,
steals
the
truth
before
it
can
settle
in.
Rocky
soil?
That's
the
heart
that
gets
excited
at
first.
"Yes,
Lord!
I
believe!"
But
when
trouble
comes,
when
faith
costs
somethin'
—
they're
gone.
Thorny
ground?
That's
the
heart
choked
by
worry,
riches,
pleasures
of
this
world.
Hears
the
Word,
but
it
gets
crowded
out.
No
room
to
grow.
But
good
soil
—
that's
the
honest
heart.
Hears,
understands,
holds
on
tight.
Bears
fruit
that
lasts.
Changes
lives,
helps
others,
stays
faithful
through
seasons.
So
which
soil
are
you,
friend?
Don't
answer
quick
—
think
honest.
God's
Word
falls
the
same
on
everyone.
The
difference
is
what
we
do
with
it.
Good
news
—
soil
can
change.
Hard
hearts
can
be
broken
up.
Shallow
ground
can
be
deepened.
Thorns
can
be
pulled
out.
Maybe
tonight's
the
night
your
heart
becomes
good
soil.
Let
His
Word
take
root
deep.
Don't
let
the
birds
steal
it.
Grow
them
roots
down
where
storms
can't
shake
you.
And
watch
God
bring
a
harvest
from
your
life
you
never
imagined.
If
this
Word
took
root
in
your
heart
tonight,
type
AMEN
in
the
comments.
And
hit
that
subscribe
button
if
you
want
to
keep
growin'
in
God's
truth
together.